uwgb.edu 2019-03-05

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
State of Wisconsin laws exist to ensure that government is open and that the public has a right to access appropriate
records and information possessed by state government. At the same time, there are exceptions to the public's right
to access public records provided by both state and federal laws. These exceptions include the privacy of individuals.
Information collected at this site becomes public record and may be subject to inspection and copying by the public,
unless an exception in law exists. During your visit to the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay’s website, information
that is not readily identifiable to an individual is automatically collected and stored. This information is used solely to
improve our web services. For more detail on our privacy policy, please see the expanded statement following.
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay collects, uses, maintains and
discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.uwgb.edu website ("Site"). This privacy
policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by the University of Wisconsin-Green Bay.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when
Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other
activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate,
name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will
collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can
always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain
Site related activities.
Non-personal identification
information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-
personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, mobile device, or other
device you use to access our Site, and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as
the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. We use this information
in an aggregate fashion to track access to uwgb.edu. At no time do we disclose site usage by individual IP
addresses. Web server logs are retained on a temporary basis and then deleted from our systems.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for
record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser
to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not
function properly. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer
better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better
understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our
behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
How we use collected information
The University of Wisconsin-Green Bay may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

      •   To improve customer service
          Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
      •   To personalize user experience
          We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources
          provided on our Site.
      •   To improve our Site
          We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
      •   To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Site feature
          To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
      •   To send periodic emails
          We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to
          our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service
          information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed
          unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against
unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password,
transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication
channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated
demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our
business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service
providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out
newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided
that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers,
sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are
not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services,
including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy
policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have
a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
The University of Wisconsin-Green Bay has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we
will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any
changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge
and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our
Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of
those changes.

Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please
contact us at:
UW-Green Bay Web Services Office
Address:
Web Services Office IS 1148 - COMPUTING
University of Wisconsin-Green Bay
2420 Nicolet Drive
Green Bay, WI 54311-7001
United States
Web: www.uwgb.edu/webdev/
Phone: 920-465-2951
Email: cs_www@uwgb.edu
This document was last updated on January 10, 2013.
